<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get-starteds on Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get-starteds on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/install/</guid>
      <description>To install the latest version of the Automation Kit use the following steps below. If you are unable to use the command line tools you can use the manual steps documented in Setup Guidance.
Ensure that you have Enable the Power Apps component framework feature in the environments that you want to install the Automation Kit for both Main and Satellite environments.
Ensure that the Creator Kit installed into the environments hat you wish to install into</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Checklist</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/install-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/install-checklist/</guid>
      <description>🎥 Want to a more visual presentation of the end to end process and install steps? Review our Automation Kit for Power Platform Video Playlist for prerequisites, solution install and Automation Kit for Power Platform usage.
If you are looking to try or install the Automation Kit for Power Platform, you can use the questions below to guide your install process
The December release also includes an automated command line Setup process to simplify getting started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/setup-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/setup-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Want to provide feedback on the setup process? The questions below help us improve the process.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/setup/</guid>
      <description>Use the steps below to assist you with creating a configuration for your environment so that you can rapidly install and configure your install.
Get started by following the steps in Install to download the latest version of the command line install components.
If you want to provide any feedback on the setup process? If so you can use the Setup Feedback page.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Automation Kit Power BI dashboard</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/install-powerbi-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/get-started/install-powerbi-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>To launch the Power BI Dashboard for the Automation Center of Excellence, you will require the environment URL for your Main environment (Where Automation CoE Main is installed).
To obtain the environment URL, navigate to the Power Platform Admin Center, go to Environments, select the environment, and note the Environment URL:
Enter the environment URL upon launching the Power BI template which you have downloaded from the Automation Kit for Power Platform releases</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
