<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xxxx Xxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/datapacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/datapacks/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxx Xx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxx xx xxxx xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxx.
Xxxxxxxxxx xx xxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxx 2022, Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxx.
Xxx Xxxxxx xx Xxxxxxxxxx (XXX) xxxx xxxx xxxxxx xxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx, xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx Xxxxx XX xxxxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx (XXX)</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/alm/powercat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/alm/powercat/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxxxxxxxx xxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx XXX xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenXxxXxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxxx Xxxxx XXX xxxxxxx xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxx xxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxx XxxXxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx x Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxxx, Xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx (XXX)</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/alm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/alm/</guid>
      <description>Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxxx XXX xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx.
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenXxxxxxx Xxxx xxxxxxx xx XXX xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx
Xxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxx xx-xxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
