<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributions on Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributions on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Authoring guidelines</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/authoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/authoring/</guid>
      <description>The following sections outline guidelines and notes for authoring starter documentation.
Guidelines Source Control Design Guidelines Home Page Reuse Markdown Pages shortcodes Table of Contents Question External Image Notes GitHub Pages Setup Update Home Page Image Badge Question and Answer Question Why was Hugo selected? Question Why did you not select some other static site generator? Question Why was Microsoft Forms not used for questions? Question Why GitHub pages to host content?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authoring Questions</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/questions/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information the format used to author interactive questions that are included as part of the Automation Kit starter.
Getting Started Embedding questions in you content Custom Functions len contains Custom Widgets Image Task Question and Answer Question Why has this approach been used rather than Microsoft Forms? Question What advantages are there of this approach? Question Could this approach be used within a Power App or Power Page?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to the documentation</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Status: Work In Progress - Under Review
Learn how to start making a contribution to the starter documentation for the Automation Kit.
Setup You can use the questions below to guide your setup and contribution experience
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation Site Configuration</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/site-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/site-configuration/</guid>
      <description>In the gh-pages branch the there is a site/config.yaml file. This file contains key configuration that can be updated. You can refer to hugo-fresh/config.yaml at master https://www.github.com/StefMa/hugo-fresh (github.com) for examples.
Key attributes include
baseUrl
title params:
description
navbarlogo
logo - Note the file should be in static/images/logo
link
hero
title subtitle buttonlink navbar - Change titles and links
section2 - Change your product and features
section3 - Update to reflect key images text</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give Feedback</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Looking to contribute your feedback to the Automation Kit? You can use the sections below to explore the different feedback types.
Give Kudos Report a Bug or submit a Feature Request Look for an existing issue Submitting your Issue Other Ways to Contribute? Give Kudos Want to share some feedback on the Automation Kit or a feature and the impact it has had for you? You can submit a Kudos to share your comments with the community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
