<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributions on Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributions on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Authoring guidelines</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/authoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/authoring/</guid>
      <description>The following sections outline guidelines and notes for authoring starter documentation.
Guidelines Source Control Design Guidelines Home Page Reuse Markdown Pages shortcodes Table of Contents Question External Image Notes GitHub Pages Setup Update Home Page Image Badge Question and Answer Question Why was Hugo selected? Question Why did you not select some other static site generator? Question Why was Microsoft Forms not used for questions? Question Why GitHub pages to host content?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to the documentation</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to start making a contribution to the starter documentation for the Automation Kit.
Setup You can use the questions below to guide your setup and contribution experience
JavaScript must be enabled to view these questions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give Feedback</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/contribution/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Looking to contribute your feedback to the Automation Kit? You can use the sections below to explore the different feedback types.
Give Kudos Want to share some feedback on the Automation Kit or a feature and the impact it has had for you? You can submit a Kudos to share your comments with the community.
Report a Bug or submit a Feature Request Have you found a bug in the Automation Kit or do you want to suggest a new feature?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
