<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Releases on Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Releases on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/naming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/naming/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxx x xxxx xxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx npm install @criblinc/docker-names Xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxx xxxxx.xxx import {generateName} from &amp;#39;@criblinc/docker-names&amp;#39;const dockerName = generateName();console.log(dockerName); Xxx xxx xxxxxx node index.mjs </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/january-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/january-2023/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxx-xxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxx JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xx xxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxxxx-xxxxxxxxx) Xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2023 (xxxxx-xxxx) Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx - Xxxxxxx 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/october-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxxx-xxxxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxx xx x xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xx xxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxxxx-xxxxx) Xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxx-xxxxxxxxxx) Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx - Xxxxxxx 2022
Xxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/december-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/december-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxxxx-xxxxxxxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx x xxxxx xx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxx JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xx xxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxx-xxxxxxxxxx) Xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx 2023 (xxxxx-xxxx) Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx - Xxxxxxxx 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxx-xxxxxxxxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx x xxxxx xx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xx XxxXxx xxxxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx.
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenXxxxxxxx JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx &amp;ldquo;Xxxx Xxxxx&amp;rdquo; xxx x xxx xxx xxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/september-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/september-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxxxx-xxxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xx xxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxxx-xxxxxx) Xxx Xxxxx Xxx xxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx 2022 xxxxxxx:
Xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx Xxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/milestones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/milestones/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxx xxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx
Xxxx xxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx, xxxxx xx xxxxxxx, xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx x xxxxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xx xxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx - XxxXxx Xxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxxxx xxx x xxxxx xxxx xxx xxx x xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxx xxx xxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xxx xx xxxxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx x xxxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
