<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributions on Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributions on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xxxx Xxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx? Xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx.
Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx x Xxx xx xxxxxx x Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxxx xxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxx Xxxx xx Xxxxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxx xx xxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx x xxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxx xx xxx xxx xxx xxx?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/sample/</guid>
      <description>Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx x xxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenXxxxxxxx Xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Xxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxx x xxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx x xxxxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx x xxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxx, xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/questions/</guid>
      <description>Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx Custom Functions xxx xxxxxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxx xxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxx x Xxxxx Xxx xx Xxxxx Xxxx?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/authoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/authoring/</guid>
      <description>Xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxx XxxXxx Xxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxx Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxx xxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxx xxxx xxxxx xxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxx XxxXxx xxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxx?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxx: Xxxx Xx Xxxxxxxx - Xxxxx Xxxxxx
Xxxxx xxx xx xxxxx xxxxxx x xxxxxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx.
Xxxxx Xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxx xxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/site-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/site-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Xx xxx xx-xxxxx xxxxxx xxx xxxxx xx x xxxx/xxxxxx.xxxx xxxx. Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxx. Xxx xxx xxxxx xx xxxx-xxxxx/xxxxxx.xxxx xx xxxxxx https://www.github.com/StefMa/hugo-fresh (xxxxxx.xxx) xxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx
xxxxXxx
xxxxx xxxxxx:
xxxxxxxxxxx
xxxxxxxxxx
xxxx - Xxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxx xx xx xxxxxx/xxxxxx/xxxx
xxxx
xxxx
xxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxx - Xxxxxx xxxxxx xxx xxxxx
xxxxxxx2 - Xxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx
xxxxxxx3 - Xxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxx</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
