<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Application Lifecycle Management (ALM)</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/alm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/alm/</guid>
      <description>This page provides an overview of components that can assist you with using ALM with the Automation Kit for Power Automate Desktop workflows included in Power Platform Solutions.
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenSummary When looking at ALM for Power Platform solutions that include Power Automate Desktop components
Review the features of Managed Environment Power Platform Pipelines to take advantage of enterprise scale in-product features to manage and govern solutions within environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authoring guidelines</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/authoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/authoring/</guid>
      <description>The following sections outline guidelines and notes for authoring starter documentation.
Guidelines Goals Source Control Design Guidelines Home Page Reuse Markdown Pages shortcodes Table of Contents Question External Image Notes GitHub Pages Setup Update Home Page Image Badge Question and Answer Question Why was Hugo selected? Question Why did you not select some other static site generator? Question Why was Microsoft Forms not used for questions? Question Why GitHub pages to host content?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authoring Questions</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/questions/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information the format used to author interactive questions that are included as part of the Automation Kit for Power Platform starter.
Getting Started Embedding questions in you content Custom Functions len contains Custom Widgets Image Task Question and Answer Question Why has this approach been used rather than Microsoft Forms? Question What advantages are there of this approach? Question Could this approach be used within a Power App or Power Page?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authoring Sample</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/sample/</guid>
      <description>This page provides a sample for authoring content
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenFeedback Use the questions below to explore different feedback question types
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automation Maturity Model</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/automation-maturity-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/automation-maturity-model/</guid>
      <description>Status: Work In Progress - Under Review
Use the questions below determine your automation maturity model and discover how the Automation Kit for Power Platform or other related solutions can help you improve your automation maturity using the Power Platform.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculator</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/calculator/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command Line Install</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/install/</guid>
      <description>To install the latest version of the Automation Kit use the following steps below. If you are unable to use the command line tools you can use the manual steps documented in Setup Guidance.
Ensure that you have Enable the Power Apps component framework feature in the environments that you want to install the Automation Kit for both Main and Satellite environments.
Ensure that the Creator Kit installed into the environments hat you wish to install into</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to the documentation</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Status: Work In Progress - Under Review
Learn how to start making a contribution to the starter documentation for the Automation Kit for Power Platform.
Setup You can use the questions below to guide your setup and contribution experience
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribution</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/</guid>
      <description>As an Open Source project built on top of the Power Platform and Microsoft Cloud our goal is to rapidly provide tools and guidance to help accelerate your hyper automation journey.
As part of this journey as we incubate, mature and collaborate with the Core Power Platform engineering team based on your feedback. Using this feedback we will look to include learnings in the core product to improve and respond to your needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Stories</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/customer-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/customer-stories/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Want to see how customers or partners have used with the Automation Kit for Power Platform? This page will reference public customer stories and feedback using the Automation Kit for Power Platform.
Cineplex Read more on the Cineplex digital transformation with Power Automate RPA led by citizen developers story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Packs</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/datapacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/datapacks/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Roadmap Return On Investment Main Solution Getting Started Feedback Introduction Data Packs are prepackaged set of data that can be optionally installed into your installed Automation Kit to accelerate your usage.
Introduced as part of the November 2022, Datapacks provide you the ability to optionally import sample data.
The Return on Investment (ROI) data pack allows you to rapidly demonstrate planning, metering and monitoring of return on investment via the Automation Kit Power BI dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2022 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/december-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/december-2022/</guid>
      <description>The December release (zealous-antonelli) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the fourth public preview release. This release includes regular bug fixes and a focus on improving the solution setup using a command line install process.
With the holiday season in December and January the next release will be in February 2023.
Get Started To get started you have a couple of options
Use our command line installer steps Command Line Install Guide</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation Site Configuration</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/site-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/site-configuration/</guid>
      <description>In the gh-pages branch the there is a site/config.yaml file. This file contains key configuration that can be updated. You can refer to hugo-fresh/config.yaml at master https://www.github.com/StefMa/hugo-fresh (github.com) for examples.
Key attributes include
baseUrl
title params:
description
navbarlogo
logo - Note the file should be in static/images/logo
link
hero
title subtitle buttonlink navbar - Change titles and links
section2 - Change your product and features
section3 - Update to reflect key images text</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of 2022</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/posts/december-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/posts/december-2022/</guid>
      <description>As we round out the year with the December Release the Automation Kit team has been busy focusing on making the getting started experience easier. The December release includes a new command line based Setup.
As we head into the start of 2023 the key areas of focus will be:
Making the setup process even easier with an App Source web based deployment Demonstrating end to end ALM process for RPA Connecting again as part of February 2023 office hours to get your feedback Closing prioritized bugs and features from our backlog For those having a holiday break we hope you enjoy your time off to recharge and look forward to connecting again after the holiday season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/</guid>
      <description>Manage, Govern and Scale Return On Investment Near-real time ROI / SLA to monitor value Tools for all users End-end automation lifecycle Governance Data Loss Prevention for PAD (Desktop Flows) Automation CoE Admin &amp;amp; Governance Whitepaper Managing Power Automate for desktop Playbook Automation Kit – PAD DLP Impact Analysis Migration Manage, Govern and Scale Enable organizations to manage, govern and scale automation platform adoption based on industry’s best practice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2023 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/february-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/february-2023/</guid>
      <description>The February release (nifty-emmy) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the fifth public preview release. This release is expected to include improving the web install building on the command line December release.
Another area of investment is simplify the dependencies of the Satellite install to remove the need for Azure Key Vault.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback Questions</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Please provide your feedback to the following questions:
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/frequently-asked-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/frequently-asked-questions/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This page contains a set of frequently asked questions related to the Automation Kit for Power Platform. If you cannot find an answer to a question you have consider creating a Feature Request to update this page.
Question groups in this page: Getting Started Question: What is the best way for me to get started? Support Question: How do I get support installing or operating the Automation Kit for Power Platform?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Getting started can be one of the key blockers to evaluating and using the Automation Kit for Power Platform in your organization. You can use the interactive form below to step you through the getting started process.
You can also use the Introduction of the learning content to provide an overview of the Automation Kit for Power Platform.
The Automation Center of Excellence strategy with the Automation Kit for Power Platform can also be used to provide context on how the Automation Kit for Power Platform can help your Automation Center of Excellence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give Feedback</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/contribution/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Looking to contribute your feedback to the Automation Kit for Power Platform? You can use the sections below to explore the different feedback types.
Give Kudos Report a Bug or submit a Feature Request Look for an existing issue Submitting your Issue Other Ways to Contribute? Feedback Give Kudos Want to share some feedback on the Automation Kit for Power Platform or a feature and the impact it has had for you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/history/</guid>
      <description>This page includes links to past and future office hours sessions
2023 Planned February 2023
2022 November 2022
October 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Checklist</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/install-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/install-checklist/</guid>
      <description>Want to a more visual presentation of the end to end process and install steps? Review our Automation Kit for Power Platform Video Playlist for prerequisites, solution install and Automation Kit for Power Platform usage.
If you are looking to try or install the Automation Kit for Power Platform, you can use the questions below to guide your install process
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Localization</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/localization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/localization/</guid>
      <description>Status: Work In Progress - Experimental
Promoting inclusion and diversity in the Automation Kit using localization Goals Current State Roadmap Question and Answer Question: Is the localized content professionally translated content? Question: How can I improve the translation for my language? Question: What is the relationship to the Microsoft Learn content? Question: Can other languages be added? Provide Feedback Promoting inclusion and diversity in the Automation Kit using localization It is estimated by the United Nations that 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milestones</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/milestones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/milestones/</guid>
      <description>Notes about Automation Kit for Power Platform milestones
Work starts in our backlog, based on prority, feedback and impact features are selected for inclusion into a milestone
Milestone progress can be tracked in the Automation Kit - GitHub Project
Milestones are a guide only and not a committed timeline
Features or bugs may not ship in each milestone due to priority bugs or features
Features or bugs that are not included in a release will be considered for inclusion in the next milestone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modules</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/modules/</guid>
      <description>This page describes the key modules of the public preview of the Automation Kit for Power Platform.
Return On Investment The return on investment (ROI) modules is a core modules of the kit. The module includes
Automation Project App - The purpose of the Automation Project app is to request and approve new automation projects. The approver receives a deep link to the project screen to view all automation project details</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Compare</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/monitoring-compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/monitoring-compare/</guid>
      <description>Comparing the different options for monitoring your Automation projects as at November 2022.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naming</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/naming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/naming/</guid>
      <description>Alongside the month and version numbers the Automation Kit for Power Platform uses a code name tag each release.
Generation Process Install node dependencies npm install @criblinc/docker-names Add the following node sample as file named index.mjs import {generateName} from &amp;#39;@criblinc/docker-names&amp;#39;const dockerName = generateName();console.log(dockerName); Run the sample node index.mjs </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2022 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/november-2022/</guid>
      <description>The November release (sharp-archimedes) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the third public preview release. This release includes bug fixes and a focus on improving the data setup installation experience and release deployment to GitHub using ALM Accelerator.
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenFeedback JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2022 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/october-2022/</guid>
      <description>The October release (upbeat-dhawan) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the second public preview release. This release is a documentation only release and the release assets remain unchanged since the September release.
Get Started Try out Get Started Guide or join our Office Hours
Prior Release September 2022 (vibrant-elion) Next Release November 2022 (sharp-archimedes) Project Milestone Automation Kit - October 2022
Review the Milestone Notes for further information</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/</guid>
      <description>Register 📆 Register for our office hours session https://aka.ms/ak4ppofficehours
Visit our November 2022 landing page for more information and give feedback.
History Visit our History page for links to previous / planned office hours.
Tell Me More This meeting is a regular forum for customers and partners to learn and ask questions about the Automation Kit for Power Platform. Come prepared to ask questions about existing features, learn how something works and new features you&amp;rsquo;d like to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/february-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/february-2023/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Automation Kit for Power Platform February 2023 office hours landing page.
You can register for the office hours session https://aka.ms/ak4ppofficehours to be held on Tuesday 14th February 2023 between 7:00AM and 8:00AM PDT (See other times timezones UTC -7 https://aka.ms/ak4pp-times).
If you have you already registered, you can forward this page or the registration link to others you feel may be interested.
Office Hours Format Each office hours session is an hour long and has the following format:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Automation Kit for Power Platform November 2022 office hours landing page.
You can register for the office hours session https://aka.ms/ak4ppofficehours to be held on Tuesday 15th November 2022 between 7:00AM and 8:00AM PDT (See other times timezones UTC -7 https://aka.ms/ak4pp-times).
If you have you already registered, you can forward this page or the registration link to others you feel may be interested.
Office Hours Format Each office hours session is an hour long and has the following format:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/october-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Automation Kit for Power Platform October 2022 office hours landing page.
You can register for the office hours session https://aka.ms/ak4ppofficehours to be held on Tuesday 11th October 2022 between 7:00AM and 8:00AM PDT (See other times timezones https://aka.ms/ak4pp-times).
If you have you already registered, you can forward this page or the registration link to others you feel may be interested.
Office Hours Format Each office hours session is an hour long and has the following format:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours Questions</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/questions/</guid>
      <description>Please provide your feedback to the following questions:
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/overview/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Next Steps Feedback Welcome Welcome to the public preview of the Automation Kit for Power Platform. To begin select the first page below and swipe to the left / right or use your keyboard left, right keys to view each page of the overview.
Want to provide use feedback on the overview information? If so you can use the questions below.
Your browser does not support the audio element.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power CAT Application Lifecycle Management (ALM)</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/alm/powercat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/alm/powercat/</guid>
      <description>The Automation Kit leverages the ALM Accelerator to provide ALM functionality for solutions that include Power Automate Desktop
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenGitHub Deployment Process Similar to the release process used for other Power CAT managed kits the Automation Kit for Power Platform uses the ALM Accelerator to deploy releases to our public GitHub releases.
Our internal process has a Power Platform environment for Development, Test and Production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process Advisor Integration</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/backlog/process-advisor-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/backlog/process-advisor-integration/</guid>
      <description>&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;|&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;|&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;-| Duration Total (Total Processing Time in minutes)|Duration Total Per activity|Top-level metrics currently only median and average duration which can be transformed with some customization Case frequency| (volume per process frequency)|Case count|| Resource count (Number of FTEs needed, Number of FTEs needed for Review/Rework)|Resource count Rework percentage (AVG Error Rate %)|Rework percentage|| Currency||In Process Advisor data model
Semi Automated Automation Project Using the data collected in the Process Advisor in your Power BI custom workspace you can integrate the results using Power Automate or Power Apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/</guid>
      <description>The page contains links to the release history for the Automation Kit for Power Platform.
Read more on our Release Milestone Notes
Each release will name a unique code name assigned to make the release identification more memorable. To learn more about the name generation process read Release Naming.
2023 February 2023 - (nifty-emmy) 2022 December 2022 - (zealous-antonelli)
November 2022 - (sharp-archimedes)
October 2022 - (upbeat-dhawan)
September 2022 - (vibrant-elion)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RPA Migration</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/migration/</guid>
      <description>RPA Migration Get Started Areas Of Focus Planning Management and Governance Conversion Automation Center of Excellence The Automation Kit for Power Platform Migration module provides you a proven set of tools and guidance based on engagements with customers to accelerate your migration journey. By leveraging the strength of Microsoft Power Platform, Microsoft Azure and the wider Microsoft Cloud services you can:
Realize your goals of providing cost savings.
Providing the guardrails to plan, migrate, monitor and setup for a operations model for ongoing usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2022 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/september-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/releases/september-2022/</guid>
      <description>The September release (vibrant-elion) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the first public preview release.
Get Started Try out Get Started Guide or join our Office Hours
Prior Release Private private previews Next Release October 2022 (upbeat-dhawan) Key Notes Key notes for the September 2022 release:
For customers upgrading from the April private preview release the Private Preview Upgrade include notes on steps required to unregister plugin actions no longer required in the September public preview release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/setup-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/setup-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Want to provide feedback on the setup process? The questions below help us improve the process.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/setup/</guid>
      <description>Use the steps below to assist you with creating a configuration for your environment so that you can rapidly install and configure your install.
Get started by following the steps in Install to download the latest version of the command line install components.
If you want to provide any feedback on the setup process? If so you can use the Setup Feedback page.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Automation Kit Power BI dashboard</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/install-powerbi-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/get-started/install-powerbi-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>To launch the Power BI Dashboard for the Automation Center of Excellence, you will require the environment URL for your Main environment (Where Automation CoE Main is installed).
To obtain the environment URL, navigate to the Power Platform Admin Center, go to Environments, select the environment, and note the Environment URL:
Enter the environment URL upon launching the Power BI template which you have downloaded from the Automation Kit for Power Platform releases</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Index</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/content/</guid>
      <description>Location: / Location: /backlog/ Location: /contribution/ Location: /features/ Location: /get-started/ Location: /office-hours/ Location: /posts/ Location: /releases/ Location: / Automation Kit - Calculator
Automation Kit - Site Index
Automation Kit - Contribution
Automation Kit - Customer stories
Automation Kit - Features
Automation Kit - Frequently Asked Questions
Automation Kit - Getting Started
Automation Kit - Localization
Automation Kit - RPA Migration
Automation Kit - Modules
Automation Kit - Monitoring Compare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/support/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started The Getting Started Guidance provides some interactive questions to link you to sources of information that could help you to get started.
Getting further support Guidance on getting further support for the Automation Kit for Power Platform:
Refer to our Feedback and support page for general guidance
Use our Automation Kit Learn pages to step through the install and usage instructions
Use the Automation Kit Issues templates for search for known Bugs / Feature gaps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unregister</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/unregister/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/unregister/</guid>
      <description>Please use the question below to cancel your auto registration for Automation Kit for Power Platform. We will send you a confirmation code that you can use to confirm unregistration
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unregister Confirmation</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/unregister-confirm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/office-hours/unregister-confirm/</guid>
      <description>Please use the questions below to confirm your unregistration.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
