<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Application Lifecycle Management (ALM)</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/alm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/alm/</guid>
      <description>This page provides an overview of components that can assist you with using ALM with the Automation Kit for Power Automate Desktop workflows included in Power Platform Solutions.
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenSummary When looking at ALM for Power Platform solutions that include Power Automate Desktop components
Review the features of Managed Environment Power Platform Pipelines to take advantage of enterprise scale in-product features to manage and govern solutions within environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Packs</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/datapacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/datapacks/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Roadmap Return On Investment Main Solution Getting Started Feedback Introduction Data Packs are prepackaged set of data that can be optionally installed into your installed Automation Kit to accelerate your usage.
Introduced as part of the November 2022, Datapacks provide you the ability to optionally import sample data.
The Return on Investment (ROI) data pack allows you to rapidly demonstrate planning, metering and monitoring of return on investment via the Automation Kit Power BI dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power CAT Application Lifecycle Management (ALM)</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/alm/powercat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/alm/powercat/</guid>
      <description>The Automation Kit leverages the ALM Accelerator to provide ALM functionality for solutions that include Power Automate Desktop
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenGitHub Deployment Process Similar to the release process used for other Power CAT managed kits the Automation Kit for Power Platform uses the ALM Accelerator to deploy releases to our public GitHub releases.
Our internal process has a Power Platform environment for Development, Test and Production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/scheduler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/en-gb/features/scheduler/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Cloud Flows Calendar Views Day, Week, Month Views Schedule Run Now Open Grid View Read-only behavior of scheduled flows Error Messages Error Message: &amp;ldquo;InvalidArgument - Cannot find a valid connection associated with the provided connection reference.&amp;rdquo; Notes Install Roadmap Feedback Introduction The Automation Kit Automation Center Scheduler page allows you to view the schedule of recurring Power Automate Cloud flows inside Solutions that include calls to Power Automate Desktop flows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
