<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Releases on Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Releases on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>April 2023 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/april-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/april-2023/</guid>
      <description>For the April release of the Automation Kit for Power Platform we are excited to announce that we have made some key changes to our Satellite Solution. We have removed the need for Azure Key Vault and replaced it with a Dataverse Plugin that uses Application User security instead of values from Key Vault.
The updated Dataverse plugin will return a list of Solution Artifacts using Application User you provide. Permissions to run the Plugin are managed by new Power Platform Role-based access security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2022 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/december-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/december-2022/</guid>
      <description>The December release (zealous-antonelli) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the fourth public preview release. This release includes regular bug fixes and a focus on improving the solution setup using a command line install process.
With the holiday season in December and January the next release will be in February 2023.
Get Started To get started you have a couple of options
Use our command line installer steps Command Line Install Guide</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2023 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/february-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/february-2023/</guid>
      <description>The February release (nifty-emmy) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the fifth public preview release. This release focuses on adding a new Scheduler functionality to allow users to see the recurring schedules Power Automate Cloud flows that include calls to Power Automate Desktop flows.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Get Started Try out Get Started Guide or join our Office Hours
Prior Release December 2022 (zealous-antonelli) Next Release March 2023 (nifty-emmy) Project Milestones Automation Kit - February 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2023 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/march-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/march-2023/</guid>
      <description>The March release of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the sixth public preview release. This release focused on the following:
Further scheduler updates to filter by Machine / Machine Group and Run Power Automate Desktop flow Update to support v1 an v2 schema Get Started Try out Get Started Guide or join our Office Hours
Prior Release February 2023 Next Release April 2023 Project Milestones Automation Kit - March 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2023 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/may-2023/</guid>
      <description>For the May release of the Automation Kit for Power Platform, the key work item was the first steps along our Data Warehouse strategy for the Automation Kit. This new feature provides the ability run a Power BI Report similar to the out of the box Desktop flow activity report. The key difference in this approach is data is exported to your Azure Datalake and Azure Synapse Analytics so that you can scale and aggregate data across your environments using Azure Synapse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milestones</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/milestones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/milestones/</guid>
      <description>Notes about Automation Kit for Power Platform milestones
Work starts in our backlog, based on prority, feedback and impact features are selected for inclusion into a milestone
Milestone progress can be tracked in the Automation Kit - GitHub Project
Milestones are a guide only and not a committed timeline
Features or bugs may not ship in each milestone due to priority bugs or features
Features or bugs that are not included in a release will be considered for inclusion in the next milestone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naming</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/naming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/naming/</guid>
      <description>Alongside the month and version numbers the Automation Kit for Power Platform uses a code name tag each release.
Generation Process Install node dependencies npm install @criblinc/docker-names Add the following node sample as file named index.mjs import {generateName} from &amp;#39;@criblinc/docker-names&amp;#39;const dockerName = generateName();console.log(dockerName); Run the sample node index.mjs </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2022 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/november-2022/</guid>
      <description>The November release (sharp-archimedes) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the third public preview release. This release includes bug fixes and a focus on improving the data setup installation experience and release deployment to GitHub using ALM Accelerator.
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenFeedback JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
With the November Release &amp;ldquo;Data Packs&amp;rdquo; are a key new feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2022 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/october-2022/</guid>
      <description>The October release (upbeat-dhawan) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the second public preview release. This release is a documentation only release and the release assets remain unchanged since the September release.
Get Started Try out Get Started Guide or join our Office Hours
Prior Release September 2022 (vibrant-elion) Next Release November 2022 (sharp-archimedes) Project Milestone Automation Kit - October 2022
Review the Milestone Notes for further information</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2022 Release</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/september-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/releases/september-2022/</guid>
      <description>The September release (vibrant-elion) of the Automation Kit for Power Platform is the first public preview release.
Get Started Try out Get Started Guide or join our Office Hours
Prior Release Private private previews Next Release October 2022 (upbeat-dhawan) Key Notes Key notes for the September 2022 release:
For customers upgrading from the April private preview release the Private Preview Upgrade include notes on steps required to unregister plugin actions no longer required in the September public preview release.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
