<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automation Kit for Power Platform</title>
    <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Automation Kit for Power Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>XXX Xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/migration/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxx x xxxxxx xxx xx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx, Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxx xxx xxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxx:
Xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xx xxxx, xxxxxxx, xxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx x xxxxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxx.
Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XXX Xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/monitoring-compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/monitoring-compare/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxxxxxxx x xxx xx xxx xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxx XXX Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx (XXX).
Xx xxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxx Xxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/datapacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/datapacks/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxx Xx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxx xx xxxx xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxx.
Xxxxxxxxxx xx xxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxx 2022, Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxx.
Xxx Xxxxxx xx Xxxxxxxxxx (XXX) xxxx xxxx xxxxxx xxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx, xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx Xxxxx XX xxxxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxx Xxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx? Xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx.
Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx x Xxx xx xxxxxx x Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxxx xxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxx Xxxx xx Xxxxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxx xx xxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx x xxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxx xx xxx xxx xxx xxx?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx (XXX)</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/alm/powercat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/alm/powercat/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxxxxxxxx xxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx XXX xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenXxxXxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxxx Xxxxx XXX xxxxxxx xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxx xxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxx XxxXxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx x Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxxx, Xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx Xxxxx XX xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/get-started/install-powerbi-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/get-started/install-powerbi-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Xx xxxxxx xxx Xxxxx XX Xxxxxxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxx xx Xxxxxxxxxx, xxx xxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx XXX xxx xxxx Xxxx xxxxxxxxxxx (Xxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx XxX Xxxx xx xxxxxxxxx).
Xx xxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx XXX, xxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx, xx xx Xxxxxxxxxxxx, xxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx, xxx xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxxx XXX:
Xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx XXX xxxx xxxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxx XX xxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/naming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/naming/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxx x xxxx xxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx npm install @criblinc/docker-names Xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxx xxxxx.xxx import {generateName} from &amp;#39;@criblinc/docker-names&amp;#39;const dockerName = generateName();console.log(dockerName); Xxx xxx xxxxxx node index.mjs </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxx Xxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxxx 📆 Xxxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxx https://aka.ms/ak4ppofficehours
Xxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 xxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xxx Xxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxxx / xxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxx.
Xxxx Xx Xxxx Xxxx xxxxxxx xx x xxxxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx, xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxx&amp;rsquo;x xxxx xx xxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxx Xxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 xxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxx xxxx.
Xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxx https://aka.ms/ak4ppofficehours xx xx xxxx xx Xxxxxxx 15xx Xxxxxxxx 2022 xxxxxxx 7:00XX xxx 8:00XX XXX (Xxx xxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxx XXX -7 https://aka.ms/ak4pp-times).
Xx xxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx, xxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxx xxx xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxx xxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxx xx xx xxxx xxxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxx Xxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/october-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx 2022 xxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxx xxxx.
Xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxx https://aka.ms/ak4ppofficehours xx xx xxxx xx Xxxxxxx 11xx Xxxxxxx 2022 xxxxxxx 7:00XX xxx 8:00XX XXX (Xxx xxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxx https://aka.ms/ak4pp-times).
Xx xxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx, xxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxx xxx xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxx xxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxx xx xx xxxx xxxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/questions/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx:
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/modules/</guid>
      <description>Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxx Xx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx (XXX) xxxxxxx xx x xxxx xxxxxxx xx xxx xxx. Xxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxx - Xxx xxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxx xx xx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx. Xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx x xxxx xxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxx xx xxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/history/</guid>
      <description>Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxx
2022 Xxxxxxxx 2022
Xxxxxxx 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/</guid>
      <description>Xxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx.
Xxxx xxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxx x xxxxxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx. Xx xxxxx xxxx xxxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxx.
2023 Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx 2023 - (xxxxx-xxxx) 2022 2022 Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 - (xxxxxxx-xxxxxxxxx) 2022 Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 - (xxxxx-xxxxxxxxxx)
Xxxxxxx 2022 - (xxxxxx-xxxxxx)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/support/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxx xxxx xxx xx xxx xxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx:
Xxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxx
Xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx Xxxxx xxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx
Xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx Xxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxx xxxxx Xxxx / Xxxxxxx xxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/january-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/january-2023/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxx-xxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxx JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xx xxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxxxx-xxxxxxxxx) Xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2023 (xxxxx-xxxx) Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx - Xxxxxxx 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/october-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxxx-xxxxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxx xx x xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xx xxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxxxx-xxxxx) Xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxx-xxxxxxxxxx) Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx - Xxxxxxx 2022
Xxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/get-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/get-started/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xx xxx xx xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx. Xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxx xx xxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxx xxx xxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx.
Xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxx xx Xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx xxxx xx xxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxx xx Xxxxxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/get-started/install-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/get-started/install-checklist/</guid>
      <description>🎥 Xxxx xx x xxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxx xx xxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxx? Xxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx, xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxx.
Xx xxx xxx xxxxxxx xx xxx xx xxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx, xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxx, Xxxxxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx Xx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxx-xxxx xxxx XXX / XXX xx xxxxxxx xxxxx Xxxxx xxx xxx xxxxx Xxx-xxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxxxxx xxx XXX (Xxxxxxx Xxxxx) Xxxxxxxxxx XxX Xxxxx &amp;amp; Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx – XXX XXX Xxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxx, Xxxxxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxx, xxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxxx’x xxxx xxxxxxxx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/overview/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx. Xx xxxxx xxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxx xx xxx xxxx / xxxxx xx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxx, xxxxx xxxx xx xxxx xxxx xxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxxx xx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx? Xx xx xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx.
Your browser does not support the audio element.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/december-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/december-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxxxx-xxxxxxxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx x xxxxx xx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxx JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xx xxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxx-xxxxxxxxxx) Xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx 2023 (xxxxx-xxxx) Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx - Xxxxxxxx 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxx-xxxxxxxxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx. Xxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx x xxxxx xx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xx XxxXxx xxxxx XXX Xxxxxxxxxxx.
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenXxxxxxxx JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx &amp;ldquo;Xxxx Xxxxx&amp;rdquo; xxx x xxx xxx xxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/customer-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/customer-stories/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxx xx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx? Xxxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxx Xxxx xxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx XXX xxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx:
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxx 2022 Xxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/september-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/september-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx (xxxxxxx-xxxxx) xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx xx xxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxx
Xxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx 2022 (xxxxxx-xxxxxx) Xxx Xxxxx Xxx xxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx 2022 xxxxxxx:
Xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx Xxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/sample/</guid>
      <description>Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx x xxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenXxxxxxxx Xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content
Xxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxx x xxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx x xxxxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx x xxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxx, xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/questions/</guid>
      <description>Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx Custom Functions xxx xxxxxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxx xxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxx x Xxxxx Xxx xx Xxxxx Xxxx?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/authoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/authoring/</guid>
      <description>Xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx.
Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxx XxxXxx Xxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxx Xxxx Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxx xxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxx xxxx xxxxx xxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx? Xxxxxxxx Xxx XxxXxx xxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxx?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/unregister/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/unregister/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxx xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx. Xx xxxx xxxx xxx x xxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxx xxx xxx xxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxxx
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/milestones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/releases/milestones/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxx xxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx
Xxxx xxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx, xxxxx xx xxxxxxx, xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx x xxxxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xx xxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx - XxxXxx Xxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxxxx xxx x xxxxx xxxx xxx xxx x xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxx xxx xxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xxx xx xxxxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxxxx
Xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx x xxxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxxx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxx: Xxxx Xx Xxxxxxxx - Xxxxx Xxxxxx
Xxxxx xxx xx xxxxx xxxxxx x xxxxxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx.
Xxxxx Xxx xxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxx xxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/frequently-asked-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/frequently-asked-questions/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx x xxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx xx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx. Xx xxx xxxxxx xxxx xx xxxxxx xx x xxxxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx x Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xxxx xxxx.
Xxxxxxxx xxxxxx xx xxxx xxxx: Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx: Xxxx xx xxx xxxx xxx xxx xx xx xxx xxxxxxx? Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx: Xxx xx X xxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/automation-maturity-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/automation-maturity-model/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxx: Xxxx Xx Xxxxxxxx - Xxxxx Xxxxxx
Xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xx xxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxx xxxx xxx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/unregister-confirm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/office-hours/unregister-confirm/</guid>
      <description>Xxxxxx xxx xxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxxx.
JavaScript must be enabled to view this content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxx (XXX)</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/alm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/features/alm/</guid>
      <description>Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx xxxxxx xxx xxxx xxxxx XXX xxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxxx Xxx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx.
Your browser does not support the audio element.Full ScreenXxxxxxx Xxxx xxxxxxx xx XXX xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx
Xxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx Xxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx Xxxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxx xx-xxxxxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/</guid>
      <description>Xx xx Xxxx Xxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxx xx xxx xx xxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxx Xxxxxxxxx Xxxxx xxx xxxx xx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxx xxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx.
Xx xxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxx xx xx xxxxxxxx, xxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx Xxxx Xxxxx Xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxxxx xx xxxx xxxxxxxx. Xxxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxx xx xxxxxxx xxxxxxxxx xx xxx xxxx xxxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxx xx xxxx xxxxx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xxxxxxxxxxxxx Xxxx Xxxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/site-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/powercat-automation-kit/fr/contribution/site-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Xx xxx xx-xxxxx xxxxxx xxx xxxxx xx x xxxx/xxxxxx.xxxx xxxx. Xxxx xxxx xxxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxx xxx xx xxxxxxx. Xxx xxx xxxxx xx xxxx-xxxxx/xxxxxx.xxxx xx xxxxxx https://www.github.com/StefMa/hugo-fresh (xxxxxx.xxx) xxx xxxxxxxx.
Xxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxx
xxxxXxx
xxxxx xxxxxx:
xxxxxxxxxxx
xxxxxxxxxx
xxxx - Xxxx xxx xxxx xxxxxx xx xx xxxxxx/xxxxxx/xxxx
xxxx
xxxx
xxxxx xxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxx - Xxxxxx xxxxxx xxx xxxxx
xxxxxxx2 - Xxxxxx xxxx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxxxx
xxxxxxx3 - Xxxxxx xx xxxxxxx xxx xxxxxx xxxx</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
